A Guide to the Bolling Family Association Records, 1991-2009
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Lineage Files., Extent: 12 boxes. (Box 1-12)
  - Ludwig, Margery Carter VA. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Malone, Greg (Elizhah Bowling b. ca. 1794) AL. (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Mancini, Phyllis (Benjamin Bowling). (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Martin, Charles P. and Mildred (Mary Anne Bolling m. Issac Back) WA. (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Martin, Lucy Ewing (Jane Randolph Bolling 1703-1766) VA. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Means, Donald Bruce (Susan Caroline Bolling b. 1857 m. Jesse Milton Duncan) FL. (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Megredy, Leland (Rolfe-Bolling Lineage) VA. (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Merz, Mary Ellen (Caroline E. Bolling) PA. (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Mikesell, Edith Boling (see also Young, Joyce Ann). (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Mills, Reba Davis (Benjamin Bolling b. 1776). (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Mitchell, Robert L. and Patricia Ann (Christopher C. Bolin 1786-1876). (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Moore, Raymond D. and Marjorie W. (Benjamin Bowlin(g)) IA. (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Morgan, Kathy Anthony (Rolfe/Bolling/Gay/Murray/Robinson) MD. (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Morgan, Wally L. and Patricia Hine TX. (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Morrow, Janice (John Bolin ca. 1754-1810) GA. (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Murphy, Rose Mary. (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Musselman, Mildred (Will of Robert Kinge) VA. (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Mytinger, James F. and Laura (Mary Bolling Baker b. 1720) KS. (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - McCall, John and Audrey (Laura Belle Bolling b. 1861) MO. (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - McCormick, Dennis. (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - McCulley, Jane Bowling OK. (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - McKnight, Helen Bowling (Alexander Bowling). (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - McKown, Sara K. Bowling (John Bolen 1775-1845) AZ. (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - McNeil, Leslie J. and Linda S. (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) TX. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Nan C. (Asa Bowlin b. 1831). (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Nash, Lorna Riggs (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) OR. (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Neeley, Joyce Lynn Byrd (Benjamin Bolling/Shortt) TN. (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Nelle, Mabel Bowling. (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Nelson, Carolyn (Walter Lester Boling m. Lillie Mae Tyndall). (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Nessmith, Mae Simeson. (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Nichols, Katharine (Anne Bolling Hall b. 1713) AL. (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Norris, Aileen G. (Talitha Beatrice Baker) SC. (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Oakes, Doris. (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Ormes, Walter M. and Elizabeth (John Bolling b. 1762) VA. (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Parker, Jean Gayle (Daniel Bowlin b. 1801) MO. (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Pasqualino, Norma Bowling (John Bowling) NY. (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Patton, James S. (John Bolling m. Mary Kennon) VA. (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Pendergrast, Barbara B. (Mitchell Bolling). (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Perkins, Billie and Michael R. (Jettie Anne Bowling) TX. (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Perry, Ernie (Mary Bolling m. Andrew Baker). (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Phipps, Paul J. (Hugh Bowling b. 1829) WA. (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Pickell, Randolph and Elizabeth AL. (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Pierce, Clara Bowlan (William Blair Bolling 1731-1776). (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Pinckney, Mary Katherine Rilesy. (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Platt, Shirley (William Bowling m. Monica Johnston). (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Poole, Thomas H. Jr. and Joyce P. (John Bolling 1741-1800). (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Presley, Eddie. (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Price, Janis Lea (Nathaniel Bolen 1779-1870). (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Price, William Archer and Rosalie Pettus (John Bolling 1737-1822). (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Prichard, Virginia Meade (Robert Bolling IV 1759-1838) NC. (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Pygott, Melba J. (Sarah Bowling Hensley). (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Rahfeldt, Anna Marie. (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Ray, Joe B. and Delaine (Thornberry Bolling). (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Raymond, Shari. (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Reed-Curtis, Rhobie E. (Sallie Bowling m. John C. Blanks) CA. (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Renick, Barbara Ann (Bowlings in Tennessee) CA. (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Rich, James M. Jr. (John Bolling 1675/76-1729). (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Richardson, Gerald L. (Elizabeth Bowling m. Thomas Speake) WA. (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Richmond, Anita (Archibald Bolling 1750-1830) TX. (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Riggs, Norman and Valerie (William Bolling 1731-1776). (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Riley, Mary Katherine CA. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Robertson, Bolling Lynn III (William Robertson m. Elizabeth Bolling) WV. (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Rogers, Elnora (Edmond Bolling 1807-1871). (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Romans, Agnes (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) UT. (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Royal, Jean (William Finch Bolling). (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Russell, Delores (Ann Bolen d/o Capt. James Bollen). (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Russell, William T. Jr. MD (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Salvage, Bill and Diane (Elizabeth Bolling m. Britain Williams) OR. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Schaperkotter, John D. and Cary Randolph White (William Bolling 1777-1845) MO. (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Scheibe, Kathy Johnston (Thomas Bolen b. 1852). (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Schlegel, Gary and Nancy OK. (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Schmitt, Lee (Mrs. Wilfred) CO. (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Schrader, Joseph H. and Carolyn P. (William Bolling 1731-1776) NC. (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Schumaker, Thelma B. (Mary Bolling Fleming 1711-1744) VA. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Schutt, Carol R. (James Bolling m. Ruth Carter) CA. (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Shank, Thomas (Robert Bowlan 1782-1851) PA. (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Shore, Robert L. IV and Gail N. (Robert Bolling 1730-1775) HI. (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Siefert, Donald (Rodney Bolling) IL. (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Sinclair, Thomas G. (William Harvey Bolin b. 1884) CA. (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Sisco, Johnny and Donna J. (Charles Bud Bowling m. Dorcas Webb) TN. (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Slaughter, Robert H. Jr. (Mary Burton Augusta Bolling Banister 1789-1853). (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Smith, Helen G. Rogers (Benjamin Franklin Bowlin) IL. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - South, Noah M. and Mary E. (James Bolling b. 1756) MI. (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Southerland, Henry Deleon Jr. (Edward Bolling m. Magdaline Maud Green) AL. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Speaks, Paul Dwayne (Elizabeth Bowling m. Thomas Speake) TX. (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Springer, John (John Bolling 1834-1872) WA. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Starey, Marge (John Bolling 1788-1853) TX. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Starke, Charles E. TX. (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Stein, William R. and Catherine B. (Robert Bolling 1646-1709) TX. (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Sternburg, Ruth (James H. Bolling) CT. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Stevens, Gary and Sarah Clark (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) TX. (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Stidman, Roy E. and Beverly L. (Jeremiah Bolling 1782-1852) WV. (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Strickland, Wilbur (David Bowling 1828-1883) OH. (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Sturgill, Benjamin VA. (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Susnick, Carol Buchanan IN. (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Talley, William H. III (Robert Bowling m. Anne Stith). (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Tate, Alfred W. (Robert Donathon Bolin 1822-1899) AL. (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Taylor, Hazael Hale (William Bolling m. Amelia Randolf) TX. (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Teague, Bernadine. (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Thomas, Donna M. (Lewis Bolling 1790-1839) PA. (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Thomas, Patsy Yates KY. (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Thompson, Al M. and Ruth Savage (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) OR. (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Thompson, Suzan Bolling AK. (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Tipton, Dewey R. and Freada (Jarrett Bowling m. Ann Eliza Jones) TX. (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Vander Naillen, Ralph Jr. and Mary Catherine Woolwine TX. (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Waldrop, Frank W. VA. (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Walter, James and Lois Swaney NE. (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Ward, Mary Haxall. (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Webb, Donald W. (Webb Charts) KY. (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Wetherell, Sally Ann. (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Whitfield, Jon A. and Rosina (Anne Bolling Hall b. 1713) KY. (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Whitmore, Page G. (Anne Bolling Murray 1718-1800) MN. (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Wiedersum, Fairfax C. NY. (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Wilber, Wayne Lynn and Stacy (Jeremiah Bowlin b. 1777) TX. (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Wilkes, Harold and Ruedell OK. (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Wilkinson, Gene Cox TX. (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Wilkinson, George C. and Margaret C. (Margaret Bolling Eldridge) VA. (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Williams, Betty Bowling (Genetics). (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Williams, Carolyn B. "Jackie" (see also: Clack) AL. (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Williams, Darrell (see also: Alderman, Daphna Lynette Bolen). (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Williams, Hugh A.Jr. NC. (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Williams, Kay Bolen (John Bolling b. 1794) OH. (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Williams, Sallye Pleasant (Col. Robert Bolling 1660-1709). (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Williamson, Stirling L. Jr. and Jane Cooley VA. (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Winfrey, Annabelle (Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832) CA. (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Wood, Sam Madeley Jr. and Peggy Anne Callari Wood. (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Young, Joyce Ann (Archibald Bolling (OH. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Young, Nell Smith TX. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Young, Shanna (George Bowlin b. 1801) MO. (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Series II. Chester T. Bolling Files., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 12-23, 36)
  The Chester T. Bolling files include his research notes on the Bolling family and allied lines, and compilations by other researchers. There is also information on various Bolling family homes. The files also include correspondence while Bolling served as vice-president of the BFA. Subjects include the Association's founding and organization, business and financial matters, reunions, and genealogical inquiries. There is also a good deal of material relating to the BFA's "Benjamin File Committee," which was established in 1993 to determine the lineage and parents of Benjamin Bolling (1734-1832). Other material of note in this series are typed transcriptions of the diaries of Col. William Bolling (1777-1845) of Chesterfield and Goochland Counties, Virginia, research on and restoration of Bolling family portraits held by various institutions, an index and notes to the diaries of Robert Skipwith (1810-1904) of Goochland and Powhatan Counties, and Richmond, Virginia, and information on Melungeon history and culture.
  - Argall. (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Baker. (Box 12, Folder 26-29)
  - Baker. (Box 13, Folder 1-4)
  - Baker (Harley Tucker Bowling). (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Baker, Rev. Andrew. (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Bassett Library Research - Pittsylvania, Henry, and Granville Counties. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Ben Bolen Church (Trout, NC). (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Benjamin Committee. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - "Benjamin File" (For Nashville). (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Bible of Archibald Bolling. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Blair, James. (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - "Blue" Bollings. (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Bocetti, Billie C. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Bolen, Todd. (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Bolen, Todd - Back Bible Record. (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Bolin Creek (UNC-Chapel Hill). (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Bolin, Norman. (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Bolling and Bowling Generations by Rufus B. Bird. (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Bolling, Blair - 1838 Manuscript. (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Bolling, Blair - Centre Hill Cemetery. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - "The Bolling, Bowlin, Bolen Family in America Before 1800" by Todd Bolen and Lois Stange. (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - "The Bolling, Bowlin, Bolen Family in America Before 1800" by Todd Bolen and Lois Stange (Second Edition). (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Bolling, Clay. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Bolling, Edward (1556-1592) - Descendants. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Bolling Family Association - Directory, 1 June 1992. (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - The Bolling Family: Eight Centuries of Growth - Addendum. (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Bolling Family Newsletter. (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - "Bolling Family Photographs" by James S. Patton. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Bolling Foundation - Financial Statement, 1995. (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Bolling Hall. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Bolling Hall (Bradford, Yorkshire). (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Bolling Island. (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Bolling, Samuel (Laurens, SC). (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Bolling Theatre (Norton, VA). (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Bolling, Col. William - Diaries. (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Bolling, Col. William - Diaries, 1809, 1827-1828, 1836-1842 (Transcriptions). (Box 15, Folder 2-11)
  - "The Bollings of Wise County, Virginia" by W. S. Rose. (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - "Both Pretty Young Men" by Chester T. Bolling. (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Bowlin, Delaney. (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Bowling, Darrell C. (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Bowling, Harley Tucker. (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Braddock, Gen. Edward - Published Sources. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Bradford Cathedral. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Brawley, Dorothy P. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Browder, Barbara H.. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Brown, Stuart E. Jr. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Carson, Dorothy. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Cedar Level. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Central Intelligence Agency. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Charlotte County VA. (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Charts. (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Chellowe. (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Chesterfield County VA. (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Christmas Gift, 1991. (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - The Civil War Handbook by William H. Price. (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Clippings. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Cobbs Bible Record. (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Cobbs Cemetery. (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence, 1978, 1981, 1985-1988, 1990-1992. (Box 16, Folder 18-26)
  - Correspondence, 1993-2002 (January 15). (Box 17, Folder 1-12)
  - Correspondence, 2002 (January 16-October). (Box 18, Folder 1-4)
  - Correspondence, undated. (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Crigler, Cora Byers. (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - DNA. (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - "Doubting Thomas" by Chester Thomas Bolling. (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Eldridge. (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Family Group Chairmen. (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - First Church of Wise County. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Flat Gap Cemetery Fund. (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Gibson-Purkey-Countiss. (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Golden Hills (Charlotte County, VA). (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Goochland County VA. (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Halifax County VA Deed Abstracts. (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Hamilton, Verta. (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Hankins, Edith Jackson. (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Henry County VA Abstracts. (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Hicks, Nancy Bowling. (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Highway Markers. (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - "History of the Bolling Family of Wise County, Virginia" by Rev. C. Glenn Bolling. (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - International Genealogical Index. (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Jago, Elizabeth Fuller. (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - James, Colin. (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Kennedy-Edwards. (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Lake, Willis W. (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Lake, Willis W. (Benjamin Bolling File Committee). (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Land Patents. (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Lemay. (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - "The Lineage of Benjamin Bolling 1734-1832" by Willis W. Lake. (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Lunenburg County VA. (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - McConnaughey, Gibson and Cary. (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - McKelway, Bill. (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - McKinley, Jill (Benjamin File Committee). (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Meek. (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Melungeons. (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Melungeons (Kennedy). (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - A Memoir of a Portion of the Bolling Family in England and Virginia. (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Minutes - Bolling Family Association Board of Directors, 27 June 1995. (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous. (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Mytinger, Laura Dee. (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Nashville Reunion Handouts. (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Navy Separation Notice. (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - North Carolina Records. (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Northern Neck. (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Notebook. (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Notebook. (Box 20, Folder 2-11)
  - "Notes on the Bolling and Short Families of Pound Valley" by Chester T. Bolling. (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Notes on the Early Bollings, of Bolling" by Eleanor Blanche Tempest. (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - "Of Whom I Came; From Where I Came..." Volume VI, Part I (Bolling Volume) by Zelma Wells Price. (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Orange County NC. (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Orange County NC. (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Parish Registers. (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Parks, Joseph. (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Patton, James S.. (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Photographs. (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Pittsylvania County VA. (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Pocahontas. (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Portrait - Capt. Bolling. (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Portraits. (Box 21, Folder 9-10)
  - Powhatan Bolling vs. Powhatan Boulding. (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Pratt, Annie S. (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Prince Edward County VA. (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Published Sources. (Box 21, Folder 14-15)
  - Randolph, Brett Jr. (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Ray, Katherine P. (Benjamin Bolling Project). (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Ray, Katherine Parsons (Benjamin File Committee). (Box 22, Folder 2-3)
  - Reunion Discussion Paper,1992. (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - "Robert Bolling and the Bailment of Colonel Chiswell" by J.A. Leo Lemay. (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Russell County VA Census. (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Skipwith, Robert - Diary Index and Notes. (Box 22, Folder 7-9)
  - Slaughter. (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Slaughter-Bouldin Research - Bassett Library. (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Software. (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Speech - "1776-10". (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Spencer. (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Stabile, Susan M. - Williamsburg Talk, 25 June 1993. (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Stafford County VA. (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Stallard, Wilma R.. (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Stifter, Lee (Stoneman Notes). (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - "The Story of Virginia: Getting to the Sources" - Virginia Historical Society. (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - "Varina on the James". (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - The Virginia Adventure - Roanoke to Jamestowne: An Archaeological and Historical Odyssey by Ivor Noel Hume. (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - The Virginia Genealogist - Index. (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Wallin. (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Ward. (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Welsh, Jean J. (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Wills and Inventories - Virginia - Index. (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Wills, Jeffrey. (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Wise High School Reunion, 1 July 2000. (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Wytheville Cemetery. (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Series III. Colin James Files., Extent: 4 boxes. (Box 23-26)
  The Colin James files include his early research on the Bolling family for a book he intended to publish. There is correspondence and notes, as well as questionnaires completed by numerous Bolling descendants. This series also contains material James accumulated while serving on the Genealogy Committee of the BFA, including the same type of records that can be found in the lineage files, and there is also information relating to the Association's founding. Finally, this series also contains genealogical material on the Bell, Clack, Crandall, Eggleston, Feild, and Harrison families.
  - Aston. (Box 23, Folder 11)